(Sheldon on laptop screen:)Greetings. As you know, I'm not
comfortable with prolonged goodbyes...
(Sheldon:)...and maudlin displays of emotion,
so I've prepared this short video.
(Sheldon on laptop screen:)The four of you are three of my closest
friends and one treasured acquaintance.
(Sheldon on laptop screen:)Though I cannot state categorically
that my life will be diminished...
(Sheldon on laptop screen:)...by not having you in it, I am
comfortable if you choose to believe that.
(Sheldon on laptop screen:)Since you intend to remain
in this lawless metropolitan area...
(Sheldon on laptop screen:)...statistics suggest that you will
succumb to tragic and gruesome ends...
(Sheldon on laptop screen:)...before we meet again.
Live long and prosper.
(Penny:)Sheldon, that's so--
You might wanna lock the door
behind me. This isn't Bozeman.